<changelog>
	<changes>
		<version>0.1</version>
		<change>Initial Release.</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.2</version>
		<change>Fixed 99% of all resizing Issues. And as a small christmas present/easter egg, double tap the grabber when you have an app open in the reachability view :)</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.2.5</version>
		<change>Icons are now Properly aligned and sized in the App Selector views</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.3</version>
		<change>Fully Fixed App Selectors. Now Show app labels, updated/beta dots and badges</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.4</version>
		<change>Fixed Black screen bug. But the bug still happens when running apps inside windows</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.5</version>
		<change>Now adds Aura and Empoleon from Multiplexer. Black screen still happens with empoleon and the vpn bug are still left to fix</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.5.4</version>
		<change>Readded windows themes from Multiplexer and adds optional Activator Gestures</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.6</version>
		<change>Fixed 9.1 compatibility. Still need to fix black screen bugs</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.6.2</version>
		<change>Fixed Black Screen bug with windows on home screem. Fixed Hash sum when downloading. Colored prefs to make them a little prettier</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.6.3</version>
		<change>Fixed startup crash due to typo</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.7</version>
		<change>Fixed not being able to launch apps from HS when running app in window. I say the tweak is pretty stable, but I need more reports to see if all the bugs have been fixed</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.7.2</version>
		<change>Fixed crashes caused by a typo and Asphaleia</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.7.9</version>
		<change>Fixed THE startup crash, fixed audio issues? Fixed VPN bug, may have fixed 10.X crash but not sure. Unfortunately in order to fix the startup crash, I had to kill ios 8 support (if people used zypen on ios 8 sorry)</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>0.8</version>
		<change>Sorry for lack of updates, was busy updating all of Multiplexer for Elijah Frederickson (95% done). Fixed assertiond hook (not sure of implications but should fix backgronding issues) and made the Daemon actually work. Still working on launch crashes</change>
	</changes>
		<version>0.9</version>
		<change>I THINK I FIXED THE STARTUP CRASH!!! That and a better iOS 10 compatibility.</change>
	</changes>
	</changes>
		<version>0.9.1</version>
		<change>Fixed crash when clicking home button.</change>
	</changes>
</changelog>
