<changelog>
	<changes>
		<version>1.0</version>
		<change>Initial Release</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>1.0-41</version>
		<change>Tried redoing prefs, gave up cuz nothing worked and current method decided to fix itself. Added app blacklisting and option to only enable/disable spring animations. Next is reset button, kinda need help on that</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>1.1</version>
		<change>Added App Exemptions, On/Off for spring animations, and option to only enable in Spring Board</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>1.1-1</version>
		<change>Internal Changes (switched from float to double cuz y not)</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>1.2</version>
		<change>Major Preference rewrite (doesnt require respring anymore yay!) but i did have to remove app blacklisting for now (sorry). Changes to sliders now for convinience and to prevent yall from bootlooping, up next is the reset prefs button (im getting there). And the infinite update loop should've been fixed but nope, can someone help me with this. YOU CAN TAP THE VALUE NEXT TO SLIDER TO ENTER AN EXACT VALUE</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>1.2.1</version>
		<change>Mixed bag of an update. Fixed/re-added appblacklisting/only eanbling bounce in springboard. But I unfortunatly had to remove the ability to add a precise value by tapping the value next to the slider (it became unstable in compling the tweak). I am also getting reports that the last update was causing crashes in Facebook/Messenger, can yall confirm that this is true and Hortus actually is the cause? Email me if so. Sorry about lack of updates, school is ramping up. Yes a reset button is in the works, not sure how to do it tho </change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>1.2.1.1</version>
		<change>Hopefully fixed facebook and other apps crashing. Email me if apps are still crashing. Tweak is almost done, just need to added a reset prefs option and readd betterpstableslidercell(alows you to tap the value on teh slider to set an exact value)</change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>1.3</version>
		<change>Probably last beta because it seems done To me, will submit to BigBoss soon unless there are issues. Added Reset Prefs and BetterPSSliderTableCell. Last Chance to Email me Issues.</change>
	</changes>
</changelog>
